[whistling]
[Winnie the Pooh theme song]
[male narrator] This could be
the room of any small boy.
But, in fact, it's not.
It is the room of one young boy
in particular named Christopher Robin.
Now, Christopher Robin
has a very active imagination,
not to mention the uncanny ability
to collect things.
Big things. Small things. Sticky things.
But his favourite things
are his stuffed animals.
Ah! There they are now.
A charming and eccentric
cast of characters.
And his best friend among them
is a bear named Winnie the Pooh.
Or Pooh for short.
Together they had many
unusual adventures,
that all happened right here
in the Hundred Acre Wood.
♪ Deep in the Hundred Acre Wood
♪ Where Christopher Robin plays
♪ You'll find the enchanted
neighbourhood
♪ Of Christopher's childhood days
♪ A donkey named Eeyore is his friend
♪ And Kanga and little Roo
and Tigger, too
♪ There's Rabbit and Piglet
and there's Owl
♪ But most of all Winnie the Pooh
♪ Winnie the Pooh
Winnie the Pooh
♪ Tubby little cubby
all stuffed with fluff
♪ He's Winnie the Pooh
Winnie the Pooh
♪ Willy-nilly silly old bear
♪ Winnie the Pooh
Winnie the Pooh
♪ Tubby little cubby
all stuffed with fluff
♪ He's Winnie the Pooh
Winnie the Pooh